[Music]
[Música]
How's it going family how are you I hope you're
qué tal familia cómo estáis espero que
enjoying the day and we're
estéis disfrutando del día y nosotros
here with salsa well you know that
aquí con el salsa bueno ya sabéis que
right now the topic of coco is trending
ahora mismo es tendencia el tema de coco
because dallas released a video
porque dallas le ha sacado un vídeo
where he exposed it okay and thank you very much
donde lo ha expuesto vale y muchísimas
and congratulations for that 10 tables
gracias y felicidades por eso 10 mesas
are no we remind you all that you can
son no recordamos a todos que podéis
subscribe
suscribiros
that the subscription is completely free
que es completamente gratis la
okay here the salsa you
suscripción vale aquí el salsero lo
can enjoy it even if you don't have
podéis disfrutar aunque no tengáis un
money you can subscribe you
pavo podéis suscribiros
can become members if you want you can
podéis haceros miembros si queréis
give members which is also
podéis regalar miembros que también se
possible like in tweets
puede como en tweets
and you can even eat my mouth you can I would like to I
e incluso podéis comerme la boca podéis
said but what I do want
ya quisiera dije pero lo que sí quiero
you to do is like and comment on
que hagáis darle like y estar comentando
the chi - basically
el chi - básicamente salió al reflote
a gossip came to the surface okay it's a gossip from a
un chisme vale que es un chisme de hace
while ago but it has resurfaced
tiempo pero que ha vuelto a reflotar
this afternoon romina thank you very much
esta tarde romina muchas gracias
congratulations on those 16 months and it's that
felicidades por esos 16 meses y es que
with that he
con q
insulted aurum play in his day and despite the fact
insulto en su día a aurum play y a pesar
that he insulted auron play when he already
de que insultó a auron play cuando ya se
started to hang out with the group and when he
empezó a juntar con el grupito y cuando
already started  to grow and become famous milestone
ya empezó a crecer y hacerse famoso hito
the income this well as they already
el rédito este pues como que ya se
greet each other and shake hands okay let's
saludan y se dan la mano vale vamos a
see a little bit the whole context okay because
ver un poco todo el contexto vale porque
there are people who say that cause q
hay gente que dice que que cause q se
apologized to auguró but I've been
disculpó con auguró pero yo he estado
looking here for all the clicks possible
buscando aquí todos los clicks posibles
and that apology doesn't exist what I'm
y no existe esa disculpa que estoy
saying
diciendo
the most and besides an Argentine
lo máximo y aparte un argentino
apologizing I see it very complicated
disculpándose lo veo muy complicado
but there will be an Argentine joke and no but
pero habrá una broma argentina y no pero
a little if it is literally
un poco si es literalmente
literally he has not apologized the
literalmente no se ha disculpado lo
most he says in an interview that I'm
máximo que dice en una entrevista que os
going to put you
voy a poner
well but it's that I really auro it's not that
bueno pero es que yo en verdad auro no
the rest of the videos the rest of the
es que el resto de vídeos el resto de
videos if I like them or the rest of the videos I
vídeos si me gusta o el resto de vídeos
don't criticize them I wrote that video and
no los critico yo escribí ese vídeo y
that video I think that he
ese vídeo pienso eso
never apologized nor will he
nunca se disculpó ni lo hará
but I say that's how these groups are on
pero digo así son los grupos estos de
YouTube and many times the good that I say
youtube y muchas veces el bien que digo
that there is in this world
que hay en este mundo
as it has numbers and suddenly they have
como tiene números y de repente se han
become fashionable and they are succeeding and whatever it was that has made
puesto de moda y lo están triunfando y
this kid so big he can
hecho tan grande este chico puede
outline his eyes with these masks and
delinear los ojos con estas máscaras y
well they invite him to events despite
pues lo invitan a los eventos a pesar de
the nonsense of the  that we have
las burradas de la que nos hemos
found out look what he is saying about
enterado mira lo que está hablando de
them
ellos
to me like every time he sees me he gives me five
a mí como cada vez que me ve me da cinco
kisses it is an incredible thing and I hugged
besos es una cosa increíble y la abrace
Momo and very lucky she is very well he
a momo y mucha suerte que está muy bien
looked at me he said I am going to beat the hell out of him he
me miró me dijo lo voy a [__] a piñas
looked at me and said seen already at the weigh-in
me miró y me dijo vista ya en el pesaje
and I said yes and he saw him a little bit
y yo le dije sí y lo vio un poquito
come out there very badly
salir allí muy mal
the tube provokes he was provoking me at
el tubo provoca me estuvo provocando en
the weigh-in and I have never held out so much
el pesaje y yo no había aguantado tanto
in my life Auron in my life I have never had
en mi vida auron en mi vida había tenido
so much patience that catches me in another
tanta paciencia eso me pilla en otro
moment of my life and I beat him to death
momento de mi vida y lo mató ahí a palos
every time Momo gives me 5
cada vez que me de momo me da 5
I think he is a person that well if we
yo creo que es una persona que bueno si
add this up we add 2 plus 2 we add up to what he
sumamos esto sumamos 2 más 2 nos sumamos
is telling him although he told me
esto que está contando aunque le dijo
that he is taking the
que se está tomando en serio el tema del
weigh-in of the evening seriously of everything return to the
pesaje de la velada de todo regrese a
d
los d
to what he did with Wind he kicked me out for a
a lo que hizo con wind me echó por un
disgusting joke of course
chiste desagradable por supuesto
unfortunate at that moment about
desafortunado en ese momento sobre
Maradona telling someone that when
maradona decirle a alguien que cuando
you go to Spain you are going to look for him to
vayas a españa lo vas a buscar para
attack him
agredirle
delano
délano
of the anus
del ano
total that  People are starting to tell me
total que me empieza a decir la gente
that there's an episode where [ __ ] the
que hay un episodio en el que [__] el
[ __ ] mouse Ivan when you're going to send me
[__] ratón iván cuando me vas a mandar
my time on my keyboard
mi rato de mi teclado
with Javi you have to click where he
con javi tienes que poner el click donde
insults Aurum Play in a very brutal way and
insulta de forma muy bestia aurum play y
then at the evening he shakes his hand well I could
luego en la velada le da la mano bueno
n't find the click where he shakes his
no encontraba el click donde le da la
hand but the video is there because
mano pero sí que está el vídeo porque es
in fact he has it uploaded to his
que de hecho es que lo tiene subido a su
channel, I mean there's no no no no
canal o sea no hay ningún no hay ningún
apology
ninguna disculpa
like a lot of people are telling me no but he already
como me dice mucha gente no pero ya se
apologized in fact there's the response on
disculpó de hecho ahí la respuesta del
Twitter that proposes no but he already
twitter que propone no pero ya se
apologized those apologies aren't
disculpó esas disculpas no están
Javier defending Wen I started to see
javier defendiendo a wen me echó a ver
if I can like him more but I may
si me puede caer mejor peor me pueden
think some things about him are good or bad
parecer algunas cosas bien o mal de él
but something that someone comes and I will do it and
pero que algo que venga uno y lo haré y
wants to attack him, whether we are
lo quiera agredir sea si estamos
criticizing a niche for the issue of the
criticando a un nicho por el tema del
bottle how are you going to defend someone who
botellazo cómo vas a defender a uno que
wants to attack him for having made a
le quiera agredir por haber hecho un
joke about Maradona, I mean no there's no way to
chiste de maradona o sea no no hay por
take it but it's that attacking me, I would
dónde cogerlo pero es que agredir no me
never justify an attack from
yo no justificaría nunca una agresión de
anyone to anyone, be it me I am  totally anti
nadie a nadie sea yo soy totalmente anti
physical violence me if you tell me the minor
violencia física me si me dices al menor
who asks for someone hitting your son or
que pide a alguien pegándole a tu hijo o
something that you say something very strong about your
algo que dices algo muy fuerte de tu
son or that they do something to your wife you know
hijo o que le hacen algo a tu mujer sabe
well we'll see there we talk about another
pues ya veremos ahí hablamos de otro
term
término
javi coco never apologized but it's not that he has
javi coco jamás se disculpó pero no es
excused us the one who has a
que nos haya disculpado el que tiene un
video uploaded to his channel to a play
vídeo subido a su canal a un play me cae
I don't like you guys I want to say something euroempleo that is theory of history I am always in my neighborhood a genius idiot of francisco from the bar of a kid court go whether you love him or not because you can't because a bar of a kid in a video is go
un bar de a un nene en un vídeo es vaya
but if you can take a picture of me with
pero yo si me puedes hacer una foto con
a drunk girl
una mina borracha
and everything is fine
y todo bien
with a kid there is
con un nene
no
no tiene
law
ley
the kid can be a can be an ace
el nene puede ser un puede ser un as
taurasi if it can't be it can
taurasi si no puede ser no lo puede
never vary it like that the undersigned annoying
variar nunca así el suscrito molesto
bolo leave it the cinema can even be
bolo déjalo que el cine puede ser hasta
a murderer but you can't see it leave it
un asesino pero no lo puedes ver dejar
like that it
así
refers to nor del tú the young people
que se refiere a nor del tús los jóvenes
who refer order tus is for not the one
que se refieran orden tus es por no el
of tus I do
del tus
n't believe it is for noel del tour
no me lo creo que sea por noel del tour
and that he is making this video  seriously I don't know what you do
y que esté haciendo este vídeo en serio
n't screw up my life I mean
no me lo que no me jodáis la vida o sea
the aurum video in order you most
el vídeo de aurum en orden tus muy
likely I don't know if he has said it on
probablemente no sé si él lo ha dicho en
some occasion or not or maybe I'm
alguna ocasión o no o a lo mejor me
wrong but I would almost affirm that it is
equivoco pero yo casi afirmaría que es
an agreement with nor del tus's father I
un acuerdo con el padre de nor del tus
don't know if he hasn't commented on it yet he has
no sé si aún no lo ha comentado lo ha
denied it on some occasion but I base myself
negado en alguna ocasión pero yo me baso
on the fact that nordelta's father has
en que a mí el padre de nordelta me ha
offered me agreements a lot of times a
ofrecido acuerdos un montón de veces
lot of times in fact I have
pero un montonazo de veces de hecho
I have videos look for the sabinos
tengo yo tengo vídeos buscar los sabinos
del avión and he will tell me in order you have
del avión y me dirá en orden tus tengo
videos of me telling it and proving it I mean
vídeos de lo cuento y lo demuestro o sea
the father was going around offering
el padre iba por ahí ofreciéndole a
all the youtubers big agreements so
todos los youtuber grandes acuerdos para
that they would criticize his son
que criticaran al hijo
seriously so seriously let's go I have a
en serio tan en serio vamos tengo un
video out there look for it wise man save us
vídeo por ahí buscarlo sabio líbranos
from the cough
del tos
but come on 100% I'm telling you because come on
pero vamos 100% te lo digo yo porque
100%
100%
[Music]
[Música]
here it is look nordelta's dad
aquí lo tiene mira el papá de nordelta
pays to be criticized three
paga para que lo critiquen hace tres
years ago I don't know if I can find something let's
años no sé si encuentro algo
see here the most played point the
a ver aquí el punto más reproducido la
action of one of my videos  that at most they
acción de un vídeo mío que a los máximos
can be a hundred euros at most
pueden ser cien euros a lo máximo máximo
which is normally less and because Javier
que normalmente es menos y porque javier
and Medirá you find out about these little things well
y medirá tú te enteras de estas cositas
first of all because my
pues bueno en primer lugar porque mis
colleagues on YouTube watch videos about in
colegas youtube mira videos sobre en
order yours
orden tus
or the crazy one I'm writing to you to invite you to
o la demente te escribo para invitarte a
make a video about minor del tus or in other words
hacer un vídeo sobre minor del tus o sea
this is an email
este es un e-mail
that the father sends
que le manda el padre
ah to the
ah
crazy one
al demente
what a good father he must be what a good
qué buen padre tiene que ser qué buen
father you must be for you to take the
padre tienes que ser para que cojas al
crazy one and on top of that the crazy one and ask
demente y encima el demente y le pidas a
a video to make a video for him
un vídeo que le haga un vídeo metido se
with your son the video that employment made has
con tu hijo el vídeo que hizo empleo ha
reached 10 million views and
llegado a los 10 millones de visitas y
the videos that I made have exceeded
los vídeos que hizo yo lo han superado
2 million
los 2 millones
tremendous it's
tremendo es
tremendous I don't remember there I will
tremendo no me acuerdo ahí expondré
surely expose more arguments
seguramente más argumentos
this is to me look this is an email to me
este es a mi mira este es un email a mí
but I ended up talking to him
pero yo llegué a estar hablando con él
as a joke for a long time
por guasa mucho tiempo
this is to me I don't know if I ever recorded
este es a mí yo no sé si llegué a grabar
anything with Nordelta's father I don't think so
algo con el padre de nordelta creo que
that it's a little annoying he's a kid
que sea un poquito molesto es un nene
exactly he's a kid he's a kid his child
justamente es un nene es un nene su niño
is a  little one who pretends to return that is
es un pequeño que pretende devolver que
perfect
sea perfecto
the other has hair on his balls is that
el otro tiene pelos en los huevos es que
nobody thinks about children or not
nadie piensa en los niños o que no
because this child is a son of a [ __ ] I do not
porque este niño es un hijo de [__] no
know that he saves it to the shell of his mother
sé que lo guarde a la concha de su madre
to a play but he had you were never a child
a un play pero tuvo nunca fuiste un niño
friend I do not like or I do not like a blade
amigo no me gusta o no me gusta un blade
video video I can't stand it I saw two videos
vídeo vídeo no lo soporto vi dos vídeos
and I can't stand it look how liar it is
y no lo soporto fijaros lo mentiroso que
worth that already when it is his turn to
vale que ya luego cuando le toca a
hang out with the wine or with the cool ones
juntarse con los wine o con los guays
from the internet Martin thank you very much
desde internet martín muchas gracias
here in this interview he starts
aquí en esta entrevista se pone a decir
to say that it is not that he does not like aurum play that they sent him that video so that he gave his opinion and he gave his opinion on that video okay look at my most hated video started was that he says for brom play the above which is a video in which for my part you
que es un vídeo en el cual a mi vera
have seen how in the video all the
habéis visto como en el vídeo todo el
time insulting bardeando or rather the
tiempo insultando bardeando o sea el
video is not arguing well
vídeo no es argumentando
look I think this is wrong this no no
pues mira me parece mal esto esto no no
the video is him insulting a ping ping ping
el vídeo es el insultando a un ping ping
ping and he tells you videos I saw the videos he
ping ping y te dice vídeos vi los vídeos
speaks in plural I don't know if I did  the videos
habla en plural no sé si hice los vídeos
or two videos okay but look at what a
o dos vídeos vale pero fíjate tú qué
difference with what is said here they send me
diferencia con lo que dice aquí me pasan
a video they tell me give my opinion on this and I
un vídeo me dicen opina sobre esto y
had an opinion and I give my opinion but for me it is
tuvo opinado y yo opino pero para mí es
and according to many people it is also the only
y según mucha gente también es el único
video where there will be a player carried out
vídeo donde habrá un player a cabo
function that you are only talking about that
función a que solamente estás hablando
video you know that you only talk about
de ese vídeo sabe que solamente habla de
that video that then it is true that such
ese vídeo que luego es verdad que tal
but what is that video continues giving the
pero que es que ese vídeo sigue opinando
same opinion look it will only be a video
mismo fíjate que solamente será vídeo
dude inform yourself before such and above all I
tío infórmate antes de tal y sobre todo
feel Argentine that gives us the you if I am not
siento argentino que nos dé el tú si no
mistaken the one there never stops even like
me equivoco la de allí no para nunca aún
that decade swept life in the
así como lo barrió década la vida en el
asks fanatic of everything youtuber and you
pide fanático de todo lo youtuber y vos
or youtube and collect it giving only through
o youtube y lo recabar dando sólo por
barriers and never never never can
barreras y nunca nunca nunca lo puede
see it like that it is too too aggressive
ver así es demasiado demasiado agresivo
what you are doing well I go you what
lo que estás haciendo bueno voy vos qué
line have not weighed the money began
línea no han pesado el dinero empezaba
today if he went to the hotels where
hoy si se iba a los hoteles donde estaba
the father of millionaire or whatever was
el padre de millonario o lo que sea
and he went to the hotels where
y se iba a los hoteles donde estaban
the youtubers were staying the famous at
hospedados los youtube el famoso en
any event and the child burst in
cualquier evento y el niño te irrumpía
even the mixed tables were
incluso las mesas mixtas estaban
having breakfast but no matter how much it is you don't go
desayunando pero por mucho que sea tú no
down mind with him
te baja mente con él
now something else a humorous video that is
ahora otra cosa un vídeo humorístico que
also from humor a second
también es desde el humor un segundo
just like nordelta which is that it was well it's
igual de nordelta que es que era pues es
agustín they are free he wasn't Argentine which
agustín son libres no era argentino que
was many years ago look
era hace muchos años ya mira
[Music]
[Música]
straight and I'm glad I'm
recto y yo que me alegro
still a little on the verge of
sigo estando un poco al borde de la
death I [ __ ] on the host [ __ ] I
muerte me cago en la [__] [__]
mean it starts well I mean I don't dislike
o sea empieza bien o sea no me cae mal a
the sister angry in order you that Aaron
la hermana bronca en orden tu que aaron
play friends in order you are a kid he is
play amigos en orden tus es un nene es
a kid that the dad buys him everything he
un nene que el papá le compra todo lo
expects him to do
que espera que haga
this video supported him the same this video
este vídeo lo bancó igual este vídeo lo
van gogh his studio I said it and this
van gogh su estudio lo dije y este
kid ep now it turns out that this morning
chaval ep ahora resulta que esta mañana
like every day when I
como todos los días cuando me he
woke up I started to look at
despertado me he puesto a mirar un
twitter a little bit that through that great social network
poquito twitter que por esa gran red
says
dice
the sre tells him
la sre le dice
now because when you search for dallas in the
ahora porque cuando buscas dallas en el
afternoon or not his channel no longer appears or in other words
tarde o ya no ya no aparece su canal o
the laser is telling him that dallas
sea el láser le está diciendo que dallas
has removed his channel from being from osh
ha quitado su canal de estar de osh
to that they don't appear in the search hey it
a que no aparecen en la búsqueda
doesn't appear
no aparece
[Music]
[Música]
Dada's videos do not appear here on
no aparece aquí los vídeos del dada en
the cover
la portada
I want to feel your body with all of mine
quiero sentir tu cuerpo con todo el mío
because
porque
China thank you very much
china muchas gracias
to delete your channel from your own
a borrar su canal de su propia
platform
plataforma
see trends
vea tendencias
here if you are it has to
aquí si estás
be some kind of bus
tiene que ser algún tipo de bus
because he has put the appointment
porque él ha puesto a la cita
here is the video of aríz
aquí está el vídeo de aríz
here is the video
aquí está el vídeo
no this channel is not 6 thousand
no este canal no es de 6 mil
but the channel does not appear here let's see if I
pero no aparece aquí el canal a ver si
put it here
lo pongo aquí
enter a video you already get it
entra un vídeo ya te sale
okay okay okay it will
vale vale vale
be some kind of bus it is appointment appointment appointment
será alguna especie de bus se cita cita
for example my editor is a big fan of
por ejemplo mi editor es muy fan de
Aurum Place but I still maintain that
aurum place pero yo sigo sosteniendo que
the video but I still maintain that the
el vídeo pero yo sigo sosteniendo que el
video there was going to refer to the video that the
vídeo ahí se iba a referir al vídeo que
author of the tour made and he does not get off the
hizo autor del tour y no se baja de la
donkey, that is, he has never apologized
burra o sea no ha pedido disculpas nunca
Aurum unfortunately I cannot go out to
aurum lamentablemente no puedo salir a
see all the videos they have already shown an
ver todos los vídeos ya demostraron una
opinion of that video
opinión de ese vídeo
at that time
en ese entonces
nothing I found a guy making a
nada me encontré con un tipo haciendo un
10 minute video harassing all the
video de 10 minutos hostigando todos los
haters they got desperate because they could not
haters se desesperaron porque no lo
find him but totally but well I think what are
encontraban pero totalmente pero bueno
you going to expect from people like him to
creo que vais a esperar de gente como el
do that one that makes fun of people
hacerle en ese que se burla de la gente
with autism  you understand me don't be a
con autismo me entiende no sea en plan
hater in a panic if totally
hater en pánico si totalmente
cold of everyone there is a bug in it is late or
fría de todos hay un bug en es tarde o
if you realize instantly
si se dan cuenta al instante
that I already told you or that the video of Dallas
que ya os digo o sea el vídeo de dallas
in this video is horrible I have already
de este vídeo pues está horrible ya lo
said it
he dicho
but [ __ ] it
pero [__]
seems like they are wishing it
es que parece como que están deseando
was the end of Dallas or that
que sea el final de dallas o que le pasa
something happens to Dallas I really on the part of
algo a dallas yo realmente por parte del
making the law I no longer believe that he is as bad
hacer ley ya no creo que esté tan malito
as maybe other people can be
como a lo mejor puede estar otra gente
against Dallas if not I believe that it is that it is
contra dallas si no creo que es que es
the audience for which he demands
la audiencia para la que él demanda
because the only way he has to
porque la única manera que tiene de
pass five thousand views and continues
pasar cinco mil visitas y sigue
development to a child who was a fan of
desarrollo a un niño que era fanático de
him who was a fan of him and of all the
él que era fanático del y de todos los
youtubers who were quietly is a
youtubers que tranquilamente eran es un
child who could see him traumatized by that video
niño que le pudo ver traumado ese vídeo
well active is like very cheeky
bueno active es como como muy caradura
very very adventurous we do not know how to
muy muy aventurero no sabemos
describe it because I do not know him
describirlo porque tampoco lo conozco
much today
mucho hoy
Javi handsome idol you and Dallas are the
javi guapo ídolo tú y dallas sois los
best and nn s thank you very much to Luz a
mejores y nn s muchas gracias a luz un
huge and worthy kiss
beso enorme y digno
to kill that video and well the one who made
a matar a ese vídeo y bueno el que hizo
that video is to a man and that is why it was
ese vídeo es a un hombre y por eso quedó
stuck the reality is that  after
pegado el la realidad es que después de
that video maybe when that's not what was
ese vídeo unos acaso cuando ya no sea
happening to him I want to go back to a video and
eso le pasaba quiera volver un vídeo y
draw the conclusion maybe three other
sacar la conclusión quizás otros tres
videos that I should have seen
vídeos que tendría que haber visto me
would have fixed my idea about now
hubiesen arreglado la idea sobre ahora
a Blake but that was the only thing I
un blake pero ese que fue lo único que
saw gave me the guideline to say or the
vi me dio la pauta como para decir o la
idea to say what I said now in
idea para decir lo que dije ahora en
blade that no no let's see I don't know
blade que no que no a ver yo no sé por
why but Argentines and I don't want this to
qué pero los argentinos y esto no quiero
sound xenophobic but it has happened to me in
que suene xenófobo pero me ha pasado en
arguments with Argentines and you
discusiones con argentinos y ustedes lo
know it is
sabéis
difficult for them to apologize you have to get it out
les cuesta disculparse hay que sacarlo
like the knowledge they must be
como el saber ya tienen que estar
screwed or something
jodidos o que les pase algo en plan
happened to them like you know what for them to apologize it is difficult for them it is very difficult and he never apologized to
encuentren en un evento y se salude si
Mauro never there you have it you never apologized to him now that what he said is not that serious that now they meet at an event and greet each other if out of politeness it is well plan I can go and find someone that I have criticized in a video and then I see him and
criticado en un vídeo y luego le veo y
hey the hand it's not personal no no it's
oye la mano no es personal no no es
someone personal but man do you want me to
alguien personal pero hombre yo quieres
tell you after  What he said is
que te diga después de lo que ha soltado
true,
verdad
I am very likely and there are many
que estoy muy probablemente y haya mucha
people who, if I knew,
gente que si lo supiera yo no lo sabía
I would not have invited him to this type of
yo no lo hubiera invitado a este tipo de
event, I would not invite that type of
eventos yo no invitaría ese tipo de
event
eventos
[Music]
[Música]